<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<movies>
    <movie>
        <movieID>1</movieID>
        <movieTitle>28 days later</movieTitle>
        <genre>Horror</genre>
        <moviePrice>19.96</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>126</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>8</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2002</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>The naive activists ignore the pleas of a scientist to keep the cages locked, with disastrous results. 
            Twenty-eight days later, our protagonist, Jim (Alex Palmer), wakes up from a coma, alone, in an abandoned hospital. 
            He begins to seek out anyone else to find London is deserted, apparently without a living soul.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>7</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>8</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/28-weeks-later-poster01-1-.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>2</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Alien vs Predator</movieTitle>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <moviePrice>10.00</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>123</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>8</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2004</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Directed by Paul W.S. Anderson, Alien vs. Predator follows billionaire Charles Bishop Weyland (Lance Henriksen) 
            and his team of drillers, scientists, and archaeologists, to an obscure pyramid site in Antarctica. 
            Among the icy ruins, allegedly, lies the proof of an empire predating humankind.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>7</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>8</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/alienvpredator.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>3</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Anchorman</movieTitle>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <moviePrice>11.50</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>110</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>8</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2004</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Ron Burgundy is the top-rated anchorman in San Diego in the '70s. When feminism marches into the 
            newsroom in the form of ambitious newswoman Veronica Corningstone, Ron is willing to play along at first-as long as 
            Veronica stays in her place, covering cat fashion shows, cooking, and other "female" interests.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>8</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>88</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/anchor.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>4</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Baby Driver</movieTitle>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <moviePrice>22.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>142</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>2</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2017</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Baby Driver is a 2017 crime film written and directed by Edgar Wright. The plot follows Baby (Ansel Elgort), 
            a music lover who is coerced to work as a getaway driver for kingpin Doc (Kevin Spacey).</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>8</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>88</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/Baby-Driver-366390-Detail.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>5</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Back to the future</movieTitle>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <moviePrice>12.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>142</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>3</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>1985</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Marty accidentally activates the time machine, sending him back to 1955 where he accidentally gets in the way of 
            his teenage parents meeting. Marty must find a way to convince Doc that he is from the future, reunite his parents, 
            and ultimately get back to the future.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>88</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/64-og.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>6</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Batman Begins</movieTitle>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <moviePrice>17.01</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>189</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>0</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2005</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>A young Bruce Wayne (Christian Bale) travels to the Far East, where he's trained in the martial arts by Henri Ducard (Liam Neeson),
            a member of the mysterious League of Shadows. When Ducard reveals the League's true purpose -- the complete destruction of Gotham City -- 
            Wayne returns to Gotham intent on cleaning up the city without resorting to murder. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/Batman_Begins.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>7</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Blade</movieTitle>
        <genre>Horror</genre>
        <moviePrice>12.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>123</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>1</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2002</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>A half-mortal, half-immortal is out to avenge his mother's death and rid the world of vampires. 
            The modern-day technologically advanced vampires he is going after are in search of his special blood type needed to 
            summon an evil god who plays a key role in their plan to execute the human race.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/blade.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>8</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Big Fat Liar</movieTitle>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <moviePrice>2.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>99</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>11</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2002</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Who's afraid of the big bad Wolf? Not Jason Shepherd (Frankie Muniz), who has to prove 
            that sleazy Hollywood producer Marty Wolf (Paul Giamatti) stole his class paper and turned it into a blockbuster hit movie, 
            "Big Fat Liar."</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/bigfatliar.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>9</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Diary of the wimpy kid</movieTitle>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <moviePrice>11.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>87</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>3</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2010</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Diary of a Wimpy Kid is a series of fiction books written by the American author and cartoonist Jeff Kinney. 
            All the main books are the journals of the main character, Greg Heffley. Befitting a teen's diary, the books are filled with 
            hand-written notes and simple drawings of Greg's daily adventures</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/wimpykid.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>10</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Evan Almighty</movieTitle>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <moviePrice>10.93</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>97</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>44</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2007</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Newscaster Evan Baxter (Steve Carell) leaves Buffalo behind when he wins a seat in Congress. Moving his wife 
            (Lauren Graham) and family to northern Virginia, he seems to have it made, then God (Morgan Freeman) throws a crisis of 
            biblical proportions at his feet: </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/evan.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>11</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Ferris Bueller's Day off</movieTitle>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <moviePrice>4.50</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>110</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>1</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>1986</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Ferris Bueller (Matthew Broderick) has an uncanny skill at cutting classes and getting away with it. Intending to 
            make one last duck-out before graduation, Ferris calls in sick, "borrows" a Ferrari, and embarks 
            on a one-day journey through the streets of Chicago.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/ferris.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>12</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Garfield</movieTitle>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <moviePrice>1.00</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>87</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>33</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2004</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Based on the popular comic strip, this live-action comedy follows the exploits of Garfield (Bill Murray), the large, 
            lazy and wisecracking cat owned by hapless Jon Arbuckle (Breckin Meyer). Jon's other housemate, Odie, 
            is a dim but sweet dog who frequently annoys Garfield. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/garfield.png</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>13</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Gone girl</movieTitle>
        <genre>Thriller</genre>
        <moviePrice>22.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>149</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>2</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2014</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>In Carthage, Mo., former New York-based writer Nick Dunne (Ben Affleck) and his glamorous wife Amy (Rosamund Pike)
            present a portrait of a blissful marriage to the public. However, when Amy goes missing on the couple's fifth wedding anniversary, Nick
            becomes the prime suspect in her disappearance. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/gone-girl.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>14</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Home alone</movieTitle>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <moviePrice>10.34</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>99</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>2</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>1990</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>When bratty 8-year-old Kevin McCallister (Macaulay Culkin) acts out the night before a family trip to Paris, his mother (Catherine O'Hara) 
            makes him sleep in the attic. After the McCallisters mistakenly leave for the airport without Kevin, he awakens to an empty house and assumes 
            his wish to have no family has come true.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/homealone.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>15</movieID>
        <movieTitle>John Wick</movieTitle>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <moviePrice>26.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>138</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>12</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2015</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Legendary assassin John Wick (Keanu Reeves) retired from his violent career after marrying the love of his life. Her sudden death leaves John in deep
            mourning. When sadistic mobster Iosef Tarasov (Alfie Allen) and his thugs steal John's prized car and kill the puppy that was a last gift from his wife, 
            John unleashes the remorseless killing machine within and seeks vengeance. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/johnwick.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>16</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Mad max</movieTitle>
        <genre>Fantasy</genre>
        <moviePrice>23.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>154</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>1</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2014</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Years after the collapse of civilization, the tyrannical Immortan Joe enslaves apocalypse survivors inside 
            the desert fortress the Citadel. When the warrior Imperator Furiosa (Charlize Theron) leads the despot's five wives in a daring escape, 
            she forges an alliance with Max Rockatansky (Tom Hardy), a loner and former captive. Fortified in the massive, armored truck the War Rig, 
            they try to outrun the ruthless warlord and his henchmen in a deadly high-speed chase through the Wasteland. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/madmax.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>17</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Mr Bean's holiday</movieTitle>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <moviePrice>13.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>102</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>33</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2007</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Mr Bean is going on holiday to the south of France, looking for a quiet and sunny trip in the Riviera. However,
            his trip doesn't go as smoothly as he expected when he has to face a series of misunderstandings and totally unfortunate coincidences. </movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/Mr.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>18</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Hitch</movieTitle>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <moviePrice>22.11</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>111</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>4</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2005</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Dating coach Alex "Hitch" Hitchens (Will Smith) mentors a bumbling client, Albert (Kevin James), who hopes to win the 
            heart of the glamorous Allegra Cole (Amber Valletta). While Albert makes progress, Hitchens faces his own romantic 
            setbacks when proven techniques fail to work on Sara Melas (Eva Mendes), a tabloid reporter digging for dirt on Allegra Cole's love life</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/hitch.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>19</movieID>
        <movieTitle>I Am Legend</movieTitle>
        <genre>Fantasy</genre>
        <moviePrice>17.33</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>156</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>33</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2007</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Robert Neville (Will Smith), a brilliant scientist, is a survivor of a man-made plague that transforms 
            humans into bloodthirsty mutants. He wanders alone through New York City, calling out for other possible survivors, 
            and works on finding a cure for the plague using his own immune blood. Neville knows he is badly outnumbered and 
            the odds are against him, and all the while, the infected wait for him to make a mistake that will deliver Neville into their hands.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/iamlegend.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>20</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Inception</movieTitle>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <moviePrice>15.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>143</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>2</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>2010</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Dom Cobb (Leonardo DiCaprio) is a thief with the rare ability to enter people's dreams and steal their 
            secrets from their subconscious. His skill has made him a hot commodity in the world of corporate espionage but has also cost him everything he loves. 
            Cobb gets a chance at redemption when he is offered a seemingly impossible task: Plant an idea in someone's mind. If he succeeds, it will be the perfect crime, 
            but a dangerous enemy anticipates Cobb's every move.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/inception.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <movieID>21</movieID>
        <movieTitle>Jingle all the way</movieTitle>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <moviePrice>12.99</moviePrice>
        <movieLength>89</movieLength>
        <movieQuantity>23</movieQuantity>
        <movieReleaseDate>1996</movieReleaseDate>
        <movieDescription>Workaholic Howard Langston (Arnold Schwarzenegger) wants to make things up to his son, Jamie 
            (Jake Lloyd), and wife, Liz (Rita Wilson). He promises to get Jamie the hottest toy of the season, Turbo-Man -- even 
            though it's Christmas Eve and the toy is practically sold out. As Langston hunts down the elusive gift, he runs into mailman 
            Myron (Sinbad), another father on the same quest. With the clock winding down, Langston's moral code is tested as he starts to learn the real meaning of Christmas.</movieDescription>
        <ratingIMDB>9</ratingIMDB>
        <ratingRT>77</ratingRT>
        <picture>pictures/jingle.jpg</picture>
    </movie>
</movies>
